c plus plus a statically typed compiled programming language famous for its
c plus 是一种静态类型编译的编程语言，以其
widespread use and software infrastructure and infamous for its
广泛的使用和软件基础设施而闻名，并因其
steep learning curve it was created in 1979 by bjorn strausstrup at at t bell
陡峭的学习曲线而臭名昭著。它于1979 年由 t bell 实验室的 bjorn strausstrup 创建，
labs he was inspired by the object-oriented nature of simula but
他受到simula 的面向对象特性的启发，但
needed a language with a high performance of c and thus c with classes
需要 一种具有c 高性能的语言，因此带有类的 c
was born it's designed as a superset of c which means that virtually any c
诞生了，它被设计为 c 的超集，这意味着几乎任何 c
program is also a valid c plus plus program but it also adds zero overhead
程序也是有效的 c plus plus程序，但它还增加了零开销
abstractions such as object oriented patterns like polymorphism encapsulation
抽象，例如面向对象的模式，如 多态性封装
and inheritance today it's used in a wide variety of systems with constrained
和继承今天它被用于各种内存需求受限的系统，
memory demands like the unreal engine for aaa video games programs like adobe
如用于 aaa 视频游戏的虚幻引擎程序，如
after effects that were used to edit this video databases like mysql and
adobe，用于编辑此视频数据库如 mysql 和
mongodb embedded systems like the display on your smart toaster and is
mongodb 嵌入式系统，如智能显示器 烤面包机，
used to implement much of our low-level infrastructure like language compilers
用于实现我们的许多低级基础设施，如语言编译器
and virtual machines it's so popular because it provides low-level memory and
和虚拟机 achines 它之所以如此受欢迎，是因为它提供了像 c 一样的低级内存和
hardware control like c but with high level abstractions like classes and
硬件控制，但具有像类和智能指针这样的高级抽象，
smart pointers c plus plus makes it harder to shoot yourself in the foot but
c plus plus 使得你更难射中自己的脚，
when you do it'll blow your whole leg off
但当你这样做时，它会炸掉你的整条腿
to get started install a c plus compiler like gcc or clang then create a file
开始安装像 gcc 或 clang 这样的 c plus 编译器然后创建一个
ending in cpp include io stream from the standard library to handle input and
以 cpp 结尾的文件包含来自标准库的 io 流以处理输入和
output your code will start executing from the main function to print hello
输出您的代码将从主函数开始执行以打印 hello
world we simply use standard character output followed by the bitwise shift
world 我们只需使用标准字符输出 通过按位
left operator and a string literal we can get rid of this std though by adding
左移运算符和字符串文字，我们可以通过
a namespace to the top of the file now if we want to create a string variable
在文件顶部添加命名空间来摆脱这个std，但是如果我们想创建一个字符串变量，
we can do so by typing it as an array of characters however if we include string
我们可以通过将其键入为字符数组来实现如果我们
from the standard library we can use the string type instead the real game
包含标准库中的字符串，我们可以使用字符串类型而不是真正的游戏
changer though is the fact that c plus plus supports object-oriented
规则改变者，尽管 c plusplus 支持
programming with classes a class is just a blueprint for an object inside a class
带有类 a 的面向对象编程 类只是类内对象的蓝图，
you can define attributes and methods that will be private by default or make
您可以定义默认情况下为私有的属性和方法，或者
them public by adding them under the public specifier it's also possible to
通过在公共说明符下添加它们使它们成为公共的，也可以
define methods outside the class definition using a double colon methods
使用双冒号定义类定义之外的方法方法
can also be defined multiple times with different parameters which is known as
可以 也可以使用不同的参数多次定义，这被称为
overloading and is a form of polymorphism in addition we can define
重载，是一种多态形式此外，我们可以定义
constructors and destructors to run code when an object is created or destroyed
构造函数和析构函数以在创建或销毁对象时运行代码
classes also support inheritance allowing developers to more efficiently
类还支持继承，允许开发人员更有效地
share logic throughout a program to instantiate an object type the class
在整个应用程序中共享逻辑实例化对象类型的类
name followed by the name of your object and optionally any parameters for the
名，后跟对象的名称以及可选的
constructor when it comes to memory we could manage everything manually with
构造函数的任何参数，当涉及到内存时，我们可以使用指针和引用手动管理所有内容，
pointers and references however tools like unique pointer can get the job done
但是像唯一指针这样的工具可以
in a way that's easier and safer by ensuring that only one object can be
以某种方式完成工作 通过确保只能分配一个对象，这更容易、更安全
allocated to memory now to run your code open up the terminal and use a tool like
记忆现在运行你的代码打开终端并使用像
clang plus plus to compile it this has been c plus in 100 seconds hit
clang plus plus这样的工具来编译它这已经是c plus在100秒内
the like button and subscribe if you want to see more short videos like this
点击like按钮并订阅如果你想看到更多这样的短视频
thanks for watching and i will see you in the next one
感谢观看和 我会在下一个见到你